ANTHONY MERCURIO

Buffalo, NY (716) 523-4244 anthonymercurio1021@gmail.com

I am interested in getting a full-time job. I am self-motivated, committed, and determined in achieving my goals. I am organized, responsible, and have customer service experience. I have worked as a server and host at Riley Street Station (a restaurant in East Aurora New York), as a construction assistant at Handy Andy Maintenance, and as a clerk at Larwood Pharmacy. I was a Boy Scout growing up and became an Eagle Scout in November of 2019.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Construction Assistant

05/2021 to 08/2021 Handy Andy Buffalo, NY

Responsibilities included assisting in the construction and dismantling of projects, and various apartment/house repairs.

Server/Host

11/2019 to 08/2020 Riley Street Station East Aurora, NY

Responsibilities included making sure that customers enjoyed their dining experience and completed duties such as taking orders, solving customer complaints, serving food, and cleaning.

Pharmacy Assistant

02/2018 to 11/2019 Larwood Pharmacy East Aurora, NY

Responsibilities included assisting the pharmacists, cashing out customers, solving customer complaints, answering phone calls, and ensuring the store remained clean.

SKILLS

Communication

Organization

Working with customers

EDUCATION

East Aurora High School

High School Diploma East Aurora, NY 09/2016 to 06/2020